A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Communications Office photographs, RG 20, SG 1 FA780
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Italy - Bellagio - Tom Hargrove Slides (Box 10, Folder 492)
- Italy - Bellagio - Artwork (Box 10, Folder 493)
- Italy - Bellagio - Serbelloni Coat of Arms (Box 10, Folder 494)
- Italy - Bellagio - Veduta del Borgdi Bellaggio Sul Lagdi Como (Box 10, Folder 495)
- Italy - Bellagio - Contact Sheets (35mm) (Box 10, Folder 496)
- Italy - Bellagio - Contact Sheets (larger than 35 mm) (Box 10, Folder 497)
- South Carolina - Judge McFarland (Box 10, Folder 498)
- Harrar, J. Grorge - New York, 1975 August (Box 10, Folder 499)
- Wortman, Sterling - New York, 1974 Fall (Box 10, Folder 500)
- Wortman, Sterling, 1980 January 23 (Box 10, Folder 501)
- Richardson, Ralph W. Jr. (Box 10, Folder 502)
- Alliance for Progress - North Carolina, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 503)
- Williamsburg Docket - Conquest of Hunger, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 504)
- Press Conference Announcing Energy Foundation (Box 10, Folder 505)
- Sustainable Agriculture (Box 10, Folder 506)